《星河战队2：联邦英雄》
在虫族突袭布宜诺斯艾利斯(阿根廷首都) 之后 联邦军英勇的反击
联邦军在坦戈约里拉击溃了虫族 并且在P行星掳获虫族首脑
就在此刻 英勇的机动部队更挟 胜利之姿 深入虫族隔离区去歼灭虫族
这次我们所将遭遇的战争将比以往更激烈
Our war is going better than ever.
我们需要英雄! 我们需要你
But we need heroes! We need you.
入伍吧! 你们的事迹将永存!
Come on, you apes! You wanna live forever?
服役就能获得公民权 想知道更多吗?
Service guarantees citizenship. Would you like to know more?
空军元帅部署了必胜的战略行动
The sky marshal launches Operation March to Victory.
整体战需要有胆识的新战略
A bold, new strategy calling for total war...
...在每个战线对抗虫族
...against the Bug, on every front.
想知道更多吗?
Would you like to know more?
小心! 注意!
Look out! Look out!
全体后退!
Fall back!
撤退! 撤退!
Retreat! Retreat!
- 我们需要支援撤退! 现在就要! - 是 长官!
- We need pickup now! - Yes, sir!
长官 这是机动部队第6战队请求援救
Sir, this is Mobile lnfantry Bravo 6 to Fleet Rescue,
这是机动部队第6战队请求援救
It's Bravo 6 to Fleet Rescue,
全体后退!
Fall back!
撤退!
Retreat!
何顿 珊蒂 撤退!
Horton, Sandee, pull back!
快来帮我 该遭天谴的东西
Help me with this, goddamn it!
没事的 珊蒂 我抓住你了
You're okay, Sandee, I got you,
- 没事吧! - 顶住!
- You're okay! - Hold what you've got!
- 来吧 虫族! - 托尔!
- Come on, Bug! - Tor!
掩护我们!
Cover our 6!
没问题!
Oh, that 6,
嘿 虫子!
Hey, Bug!
收到没有? 收到没有?
Do you copy? Do you copy?
布列克掩护 托尔!
Brick! Cover Tor!
- 托尔 - 来呀 尝尝托尔的子弹 宝贝儿!
- Tor, - Come and get some from Tor, baby!
奥特!
Otter!
大兵 起来战斗或在这等死吧
Fight or die, soldier!
- 二等兵萨哈拉! - 是 上士
- Private Sahara! - Yes, sergeant?
二等兵奥特已经是个死人 如果他不还击虫族 就杀了他
Private Otter is a dead man, If he won't fight, shoot him!
长官!
Sir!
扣扳机 比利! 虽然不够 但还是得做
Just pull the trigger, Billie! It's not enough, but it'll have to do,
- 救援舰呼叫第6战队 - 继续前进 救援舰在前面
- Fleet Rescue to Bravo 6. - Go ahead, Fleet Rescue,
救援舰呼叫第6战队 不在优先救援单位内 MI.
Fleet Rescue to Bravo 6, rescue priority is no-go, MI.
否决了援救!
Colt-Victor-one-niner is negative for pickup!
顶住这一波攻势! 守住战线!
Hold the perimeter! Hold that line!
- 守住战线! - 不要给我找藉口!
- Hold the line! - I don't want excuses!
我需要交叉火力支援!
I want a crossfire!
过来帮我守住这个缺口 守住这个缺口!
Get in and plug that hole, Plug that hole!
- 将军 救援舰没有来 - 我们必须要离开这
- General, Fleet's no-go for pickup, - We gotta make a move,
- 顶住! - 虫子抓走了考!
- Hold the line! - Bugs have got Coy!
我是夏福特将军 混蛋 我们需要接应
This is General Shepherd, You jackass! We need pickup!
机动部队第6战队呼叫救援舰 有没有收到
Bravo 6 to Fleet Rescue, do you copy?
将军 看到了一些影像 但不清楚
General, getting a vision, It isn't clear,
他们正在增多 我们被包围了
They're building up, They're all around us,
中尉 你是超灵者! 告诉我些我不知道的
Lieutenant, you're the psychic! Tell me something I don't know!
有个厚重巨大的东西 可以让我们离开这里
It's something massive, lt'll take us all out,
- 我不明白 但是... - 将军! 那儿有个哨站
- I can't get it all, but... - General! There's an outpost,
"三角洲酒店" 八天前被弃守的!
"三角洲旅馆"哨站, abandoned eight days ago!
半公里远
Half a klick that way,
- 撒旦之钻中间? - 虫子占了那块地 将军
- Middle of Satan's Anvil? - Bugs own that real estate, general,
在那上面没有掩护
There's no cover on the Anvil,
我们将强行突破 中尉!
We're gonna have a rough ride, lieutenant!
是 长官!
Yes, sir,
你 你 你 还有你 留在这
You, you, you, and you, stay here,
其他的出发!
Everybody else move out!
请允许我留在将军这
Request permission to remain with the general,
- 要求驳回 瑞克 - 长官?
- That's negative, Rake, - Sir?
- 迪尔中尉接管指挥 - 是 长官!
- Lieutenant Dill will assume command, - Yes, sir!
他是超灵者 你们都是好战士
He's the psychic, You're the war fighter!
带他们离开 中尉! 让它们下地狱!
Move them out, sergeant! Give them hell!
是 长官! 准备撤退
Yes, sir! Prepare to withdraw,
准备撤退!
Withdraw!
- 我们走 走 走! - 快 比利
- Let's go, move it, move it, move it! - Come on, Billie,
继续前进!
Keep going!
走!
Let's go!
跟着我!
Follow me!
- 快 快 快! - 快 快 快!
- Go, go, go! - Go, go, go!
- 离开这! - 快 快! 快走!
- Get out! - Go, go, go! Come on!
走!
Let's go!
快走!
Move it!
离开 离开 快离开!
Move it, move it, move it!
那该死的哨站呢 下士?
Where's my frigging outpost, corporal?
在这 我们到了...
It's here, We're here...
时间紧迫 下士
About time, corporal, That soup's gonna boil!
- 前进! - 前进! 快! 快!
- Move out! - Let's go! Come on, come on!
- 走 快 跟上! - 赶快!
- Let's go! Come on, suck it up! - Hurry up!
移动! 移动! 移动!
Move, move, move!
- 找掩护! - 离开这
- Take cover! - Let's get out of here!
移动! 奥特! 快!
Move it, Otter! Come on, move it,
快来! 快!
Come on! Hurry up,
- 走吧 - 快! 快! 快!
- Let's go, - Go, go, go,
快点
Come on,
- 下去! - 到那去!
- Get down! - Over there!
- 快 - 到那门那去
- Hurry up, - Grab that door,
比尔 救救我...
Bill, help me, help me...
比利 快来
Come on, Billie, come on!
抓住我的手
Take my hand!
趴低
Come on! Stay down,
不!
No!
- 来! - 来 我抓住你了
- Come on! - It's okay, I got you,
奥特 柯比趴低!
Otter, Kobe, get down!
继续走 继续
Keep going, Come on,
- 不要停 继续 - 快!
- Keep moving, Keep moving, - Come on,
- 走 - 柯比 小心!
- Go, - Kobe, look out!
托尔! 布列克!
Tor! Brick!
跟我来! 走!
With me! Move!
托尔 何顿! 让 柯比进去!
Tor, Horton! Get Kobe inside!
- 布列克 跟我来 走! - 快!
- Brick, with me, Go! - Come on!
跟着我 兄弟!
Stay with me, buddy!
珊蒂! 前进!
Sandee! Move on!
这里 你可以的
Here we go, You're all right, you're all right,
布列克! 你和 珊蒂
Brick! You and Sandee...
带1班 守住四周 萨哈拉? 把门关上
...take a squad, set a perimeter, Sahara? Get that door closed,
是
Sir!
快让开!
Make a hole!
- 让开一点! - 萨哈拉! 不要挡路!
- Make it wide! - Sahara! Out of the way!
- 穿过来 - 不要挡路!
- Coming through, - Get out of the way!
没错 不要紧张
Right, easy, Take it easy,
当心他的背
Watch his back,
把他的背包拿下来! 何顿 关掉无线电!
Get his pack off! Horton, cut that radio off!
帮她拿下来
Get that off him,
放轻松
Take it easy,
没事的 医药箱在哪?
You're all right, Where are those meds?
医药箱在哪? 可恶!
Where are those meds? Damn it!
- 上士? - 很好
- Sergeant? - It's fine,
- 上士! - 放轻松 放轻松
- Sergeant! - Just take it easy, Take it easy,
我要一个人过去接上通讯 还有我需要救援接应
I want someone on that com, and I want pickup,
是 长官 是我们全部吗?
Yes, sir, wouldn't we all?
- 我命令你 上士 - 不要靠近门那 士官
- That's a direct order, sergeant, - No-go on the door, sarge,
躺下 休息一下 你需要休息
Stay down, Relax, buddy, You gotta relax,
你不能帮他做点什么吗 托尔?
Why can't you do anything for this man, Tor?
二等兵!
Private!
接上通讯! 我现在就要救援接应!
Get on that com, I want pickup now!
- 你在看什么看 二等兵? - 长官 没电力无法通讯
- What are you looking at, private? - Sir, com don't run without power,
好 在军官学校你应该有学到一个 上士应该可以解决所有问题
Well, at OCS, you learn that a sergeant is the solution to any problem,
所以你去启动电力
So you get the power up,
他们会说救援舰怎么可能在这登陆?
They say what kind of boat Fleet lands in a shit-storm?
我在下命令! 给我去执行!
I am giving the orders! You will take them!
我要该死的电力! 现在就要!
I want the goddamn power! And I want it now!
我在等着 上士
I am waiting, sergeant,
何顿 奥特 萨哈拉 跟我走
Horton, Otter, Sahara, with me,
该死 长官?
Shit, Sir?
你应该要看看这
Might want to see this,
无线电没反应
Radio's nonoperational,
中尉?
Coming, lieutenant?
看上去是何贝克上校匆忙留下的
Looks like Colonel Hohlback left in a hurry,
那是什么?
What the hell is that?
看来我们有了同伴
I'd say we've got company,
何顿! 你和奥特去启动反应堆
Horton! You and Otter locate the reactors and fire them up,
那是啥?
What is that?
哨站反应炉
Outpost incinerator,
远离那门!
Move away from the door!
大兵为什么你还在这?
Why are you still here, soldier?
大概是因为没有人点火
Probably because no one lit the furnace,
V J 达克斯上尉
Captain V,J, Dax,
看来是个大英雄
Says here he's a big hero,
战斗勋章 青铜星章 紫心勋章 紫心勋章
Combat medals, Bronze Stars, Purple Heart, Purple Heart, Purple Heart,
联邦勇气勋章
Federal Medal of Valour at Widowmakers,
真他妈多
That's a lot of crap,
受伤过四次 拒绝很多次战地任务...
Wounded four times, refused numerous battlefield commissions...
给我
Give me that,
- 英雄 - 你杀了何贝克上校?
- Some hero, - You murdered Colonel Hohlback?
他用他的步枪和配枪
He had his Morita and a sidearm,
我只用我的双手
I just used my hands,
你使你的制服蒙羞
You're a disgrace to the uniform,
他是一条疯狗 把他留在那
He's a mad dog, He stays in the cage,
记住 中尉 每条狗都有它的下场!
Just remember, lieutenant, every dog has its day!
士官! 发现敌人!
Sarge! Hostiles!
我在这指挥 二等兵
I am in command here, private,
有多少? 我们的境况如何?
Now, how many and what's our situation?
- 看上去整个被包围了 - 我们走
- Looks like a whole damn circus, - Let's go,
士兵!
Trooper!
找掩护! 右边防线 散开点!
Shelter! Right perimeter, spread wide!
你们三个跟我来
You three, follow me,
- 他使我们太分散了! - 说点我不知道的吧
- He's spreading us too thin! - You know something I don't, trooper?
他们在逼近!
They're shifting their lines!
你 守着左边! 守住中间! 守住右边!
You, take the left! Take the middle! Take the right!
珊蒂! 回报!
Sandee! Report!
没有情况!
Nothing! No movement!
快来 狗杂种! 你们在等什么!
Come on, you bastards! What are you waiting for?
闭嘴 笨蛋!
Shut up, fathead!
- 你和我一起 - 就像掩护你的6 嗯?
- You starting with me? - Just like covering your 6, huh?
准备开火!
Prepare to fire!
奥特 起来!
Otter, get up!
开火! 开火! 开火!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
来吧 虫子!
Come on! Bug!
狗娘养的!
Son of a bitch!
后退!
Pull back!
前进! 我掩护你
Come on, go, go! I got you covered!
比利 没问题
Billie, It's okay, It's okay!
快 快 快
Go, go, go, go!
Go go go go!
我们死定了
We're all gonna die, aren't we?
把你的手给我
Give me your hand,
- 啥? - 把你的给我
- What? - Give me your hand,
小心!
Look out!
- 撑住! 撑住! - 别放手
- Hold on! Hold on! - Don't let go!
不!
No!
把防线往后拉 中尉!
Pull back your line, lieutenant!
武器!
Weapon!
我们走
Let's go,
虫族!
Bug!
趴下! 走
Get down! Move!
- 好 听着! - 到底谁让你出来的?
- All right, people, listen up! - Who the hell let you out?
- 在15秒之内... - 狗娘养的...
- ln about 15 seconds... - All right, you son of a bitch...
闭上眼睛倒数到零!
Shield your eyes at count zero!
传下去
Pass the word!
正在战斗中
Get off your ass, there's a war going on,
你们俩 跟我到侧面!
You two! With me on flank!
10秒内引爆
Perimeter burn in 10 seconds.
小心!
Look out!
来吧!
Come on!
三
Three.
二
Two.
一
One.
零
Zero.
引爆
Perimeter burn.
我需要两名自愿者
I need two volunteers,
- 你以为你是谁阿 - 主角上场啰
- Who do you think you are? - The big stick that's running this show,
- 我来 - 我也是
- I'll go, - Me too,
如果我们5分钟内回不来 那表示路上有太多虫族了
If we're not back inside of five minutes, it means more Bugs are on the way,
你是说我们还没杀光他们
You mean we didn't kill them all?
你从来都不可能杀光他们 小子
You never kill them all, son,
谁有
All right, who's got...
光
A light,
奥特 靠过来
Otter, take a knee,
- 你看到了那些线吗? - 是的 长官
- You see those busted wires there? - Yes, sir,
把他们接起来
You got the wiggle room, kid, Splice them together,
士兵 把那递给我
Trooper, hand me that...
你的刀在哪?
Where's your knife?
我把它弄丢了 长官
I must have lost it, sir,
在我队里谁要弄丢了刀子就得挨鞭子
Anyone who loses his knife in my unit would be strung up for lashes, kid,
小心那根红线
You want to be careful with the red wire,
我们有动静了!
We got movement!
何顿 照明四周
Horton, illumination round,
别开火 我们正要过来!
Hold your fire, we're coming through!
是将军
It's the general,
我看到他了! 他带了2个人回来
I see him! He's bringing home two,
他带了3个
He's bringing home three,
猜猜谁到不了 希望不是葛蒂
Wonder who didn't make it, Hope it wasn't Goldy,
我刚报到第一天时他对我很好 就是那些小事
He was nice to me on my first day, It's those little things that count,
做你那该死的工作
Yeah, like doing your goddamn job,
敌人跟在你们将军的屁股后面
Hostiles! Right on your general's ass!
快点 小子!
Come on, kid!
漂亮
Outstanding,
- 该死! 真臭 - 待会你闻起来也会那样
- That stinks! - You get so you like it after a while,
- 我不会忘记这 - 我也是 长官
- Son, I'll never forget it, - Me neither, sir,
你认为我是怎样的家伙? 手放下!
What kind of a-hole do you think I am? Put her there!
欢迎回来 长官
Welcome back, sir,
我不知道你是谁 但是你是跟我一样
I don't know who you are, but you're aces with me,
没什么将军 我只是做我该做的事
It's nothing personal, general, I'm just doing my job,
嘿 伙计 让我帮忙
Hey, fellas, let me give you a hand,
该死 还真重
Hell, I got a dog back home weighs more than she does,
看看是谁回来了!
Well, look what the cat drug in!
你该看到那该死的猫! 我们在这该死的
You should see that damn cat! We're in the shitter, huh?
- 我们有机会的 - 很高兴见到你
- We got a chance, - Good to see you,
只有坏消息
Want the bad news or the bad news?
- 我差点忘了你的刀 - 留着吧
- I almost forgot your knife, - Keep it, kid,
- 不 我不能 - 士兵需要刀
- No, I couldn't, - Trooper needs a knife,
军官只告诉士兵们死于何所
Officers just tell troopers where to die,
- 不是吧 长官? - 提防你的军官 孩子
- That's not really true, is it, sir? - Watch out for officers, son,
他会害死你们
It's their job to get you killed,
第一波进来 的可和史雷特被杀
First wave came in, and Deke and Slater were killed,
然后 一波波的进来... 那小子也挂了
Came in again and that...That kid Goldy was gone,
然后这将是...
And then it was just...
我和欧哈拉
...me and O'Hara,
这些狗娘养的
That magnificent son of a bitch,
我们挡住他们
We held them,
我告诉你
I tell you, this...
当你处境狼狈时,勋章可是一文不值
...star don't mean a hill of beans when you're caught between shit and sweat,
然后那两个浑小子出现了
And then these two beautiful bastards show up,
那两个 和他们带着的手榴弹...
These two here, and they're carrying a couple of grenades...
满身的精力
...and they got a boatload of gumption,
救了我!
And they saved my sorry ass!
我愿意向你介绍他们
And I'd like to introduce you to them,
医疗士官乔 格列佛
This is Corporal Joe Griff, Medical Corps,
技术士官 阿里 皮克
And this is Technical Sergeant Ari Peck,
我没法告诉你关于这个睡美人的事...
And I can't tell you a thing about Sleeping Beauty over here...
因为她从头睡到尾
...because she snored through the whole damn thing,
那是二等兵 苏达 长官
That's Private Soda, sir,
自我们被截断后就没闭过眼
She didn't sleep after our unit got chopped down,
啥 五天以前
Found Peck the next day, what, about five days ago?
每个人都须要睡眠
Everybody's gotta sleep sometime,
你有什么故事 皮克?
What's your story, Peck?
32技术旅唯一生还者 长官
32nd Tech Brigade, sole survivor, sir!
就是我
That's me,
在外面呆了将近一个月
Been out there about a month, near as I can tell,
真是段长时间
That's a long time,
是有点长 我想是吧
Pretty long, yeah, I guess,
那好 我们送你回家
Well, then, we got to get you home,
迪尔中尉
Lieutenant Dill,
- 是 长官! - 接应安排好了吗?
- Yes, sir! - Has pickup been arranged?
- 皮克上士 我能和你谈谈吗? - 是 长官?
- Sergeant Peck, can I talk to you? - Yes, sir?
你可以恢复通讯吗?
You think you can make this com talk and squawk like it ought to?
我会尽量去修 长官
Well, you can bet I'll die trying, sir,
- 先睡会儿等一下再试吧 - 喔 不 不 我现在就能搞定
- Get some sleep and try later, - Oh, no, no, I'll get on this right now,
很好 上士!
That's outstanding, sergeant!
你是你们机动部队的典范 谢啦
You're a credit to your Mobile lnfantry unit, Thank you,
你上次洗澡是什么时候?
When is the last time you took a shower?
等我们离开这在考虑味道好不好闻吧
Let's worry about the sniff factor after we get our asses unslung,
是 长官
Yes, sir,
如果能关上这门 我们会安全点
We could sit pretty tight if we could shut this door, sergeant,
我会派个人做
I'll get someone on it,
至少还有个家伙守在该守的地方
At least there's one man looking in the right direction,
是 长官
Yes, sir,
她怎么了 下士?
What's wrong with her, corporal?
风太干了 让她鼻黏膜出血
It's the wind, sir, Dries out the membranes,
- 醒来就没事了 - 看来她会受到很好的照顾
- She'll be fine when she wakes up, - She's got the right idea,
晚安士兵
Good night, troopers,
你们全都睡一下吧
Get some sleep, all of you!
这是命令
That's an order,
- 还有 迪尔 - 是 长官
- And, Dill... - Yes, sir,
我醒来时要一份今天所有行动的简报
I want a full report of today's action when I wake up...
解释你如何使我的五个士兵送了命
...explaining how you got five of my troopers killed,
是 长官
Yes, sir,
你们听到长官说的了 去睡觉
You heard the man, Hit the sack!
你除外
Not you, trooper,
是 长官?
Yes, sir?
释放那个罪犯是违反军法的犯罪行为 二等兵
Letting that criminal loose is a court-martial offence, private,
我以为他可以帮助我们
I thought he could help us,
你认为谋杀犯的决定比你的指挥官还好?
You thought the judgment of a murderer was preferable to an officer's?
很好 你可以在审判时把那当作你的辩词
Well, that'll make for a hell of a compelling defence,
我不是这个意思 只是直觉如此
I wasn't thinking, sir, It was intuition,
直觉?
Intuition?
我不知道你是个超灵者
I had no idea you were psychic,
我小时候这方面成绩很高 长官
I scored high when I was a kid, sir,
真的?
Really?
那你为什么不加入
Why aren't you wearing the black?
我变的很不稳定 长官
I became inconsistent, sir,
青春期?
Onset of puberty?
发生在你们女人
It happens to you women,
- 什么时候发生在你身上? - 对不起?
- When is it gonna happen to you? - Excuse me?
青春期 我听说在变成男人前那是必然的
Puberty, I hear it's a necessary step on the way to becoming a man,
你在污辱联邦军官
You're addressing an officer of the Federation,
别提军官那套狗屎
Shove that officer crap up your Buster Brown,
一个像你今天如此作为的军官
An officer who behaves as you did today...
而且在一个士兵身上发泄怨气 根本不算是一个男人
...and takes it out on a trooper ain't a man!
我不是个男人? 怎么样的男人会背叛联邦?
I'm not a man? What kind of a man turns his back on the Federation?
我很高兴你开口问了
I'm glad you asked,
我训练了一代代的人把自己带向死亡
I trained a generation of people to throw themselves into the grinder,
联邦利用完就舍弃他们
The Federation chewed them up and spit them out,
所以现在当人们说 "为了荣耀而战" 我却认为"哪来的荣耀?"
So now when they say, "Push on to glory," I say, "What glory?"
你知道什么叫荣耀? 你竟敢说自己是个英雄
What would you know about glory? You call yourself a hero?
不 小子 那是别人叫的 不过是个骗局罢了
No, son, That's something other people call you, and it's really just a trick,
当你牺牲了自己的生命 除了白痴外他们也会叫你英雄
When you throw your life away, instead of fool, they call you hero,
关于荣誉 你可以问她 她会告诉你一切!
And as for glory, ask her, She'll tell you everything you need to know!
你敢?
How dare you?
这只是一个人的看法
Just one man's opinion,
不 这是叛逆!
No, it's not, It's treason!
那你或许应该开枪射我
Then maybe you ought to shoot me,
有一些事我们达成一致
Now, there's something we agree on,
来呀 拿出你的枪来呀
Well, go ahead, Take out that popgun and have at it, soldier,
我相信联盟里的规章制度
I believe in the rules and regulations that the Federation stands for,
非常好 中尉!
Very good, lieutenant!
但是你漏掉了这些孩子
But you left out the kids,
- 什么? - 懦夫
- What? - Cowards,
他们总是躲藏在规章和孩子后面
They always hide behind rules and children,
我会看着你被处死!
I'll see you hang!
你等着吧
Just so long as it's regulation rope,
让我看看
Oh, let's see,
肉干 鸡蛋 硬面包 豆子
Got your mystery meat sticks, egg caps, hardtack, beans,
即时素食 巧克力布丁
Insta-veggie meal, Choco-pudding Delite,
喜欢吃甜食?
Sweet tooth, huh?
15分钟内熄灯
Taps in 15 minutes,
我会抓到你!
I'll get you!
很高兴你终于醒了
Nice to have you with us, trooper,
你睡了很久 觉得如何?
You've been out for a long time, How you feeling?
很好 长官
I feel good, sir,
你还行吗?
You fit for duty?
是
Raring to go,
很好
Well, that's outstanding,
还要多久我们才可以关上这扇门
What's the ETA on a door we can shut, gentlemen?
我想可以了
Well, sir, I think that should do it,
如果你坚持的话
If you'll hold on...
- 小心那条电缆! - 电缆 住手 住手!
- Watch out for the cables! - The cables, Stop it! Stop it!
继续 继续
Do it, do it, do it,
狗屎
Shit,
完了 你把这该死的东西焊死了
Great, you welded the damn thing open,
你这白痴
You idiots,
所有人都去防守
All personnel to the perimeter,
士兵 你听到了 我们走!
Troopers, you heard the man, Let's go!
行动! 拿上武器 快!
Get moving! Take that weapon, Come on,
珊蒂 何顿 苏达 布列克 快 你们这些懒虫
Sandee, Horton, Soda, Brick, come on, you lazy bastards,
我们走 快 走 走!
Let's move it, Move, move, move, move!
萨哈拉
Sahara,
你们俩去那 你们俩去跑去前面 我的OP呢?
You two over there, you two front and running, Where's my OP?
守住岗位 走 走!
Man your post! Go, go, go!
- 怎么了? - 将军 有些事情...
- What's wrong? - General, there's something...
快去!
Move!
侦察到敌人 100米以外
Scouting parties, sir, 100 metres out,
他们想干麻
When they figure that fence is down...
他们真像在富翁的葬礼上出现的亲人一样
...they're gonna show up like relatives to a rich man's funeral,
- 让那亮起来 - 是
- Let there be light, - Yeah,
- 是 - 我们有 我们有电了
- Yeah! - Here we go, We got power,
我能看到你了
That's what I'm talking about, I can see you now,
将军?
Hey, general?
- 皮克 是你做的吗? - 有点不稳...
- Peck, is this your doing? - It's a little wonky...
...但它能支持住 我希望是
...but it'll hold, I hope,
我代表大家感谢你皮克
You have our tremendous gratitude, Peck,
哦 没什么 长官
Oh, it was nothing, sir,
我回去做修通讯器了
I'll get back to work on the com now,
- 硬是要得 皮克 - 做得好 皮克
- Attaboy, Peck, - Way to go, Peck,
皮克 皮克 皮克
Peck, Peck, Peck,
好吧
All right,
达克斯对你的指控是很严重的...
Dax, the charges against you are serious...
不过我不能承担失去像你这样有经验的人
...but I can't afford to lose a man of your experience,
答应我 做你身为一个军官该做的
Give me your word as an officer you'll do your duty,
我不再是个军官了 将军 但是我以男人的尊严答应你
I'm no longer an officer, general, but I'll give you my word as a man,
你的军衔恢复 直到你的罪行或清白...
Your rank is restored until your guilt or innocence...
被听证会裁决
...is determined by a hearing,
我可以向你坦承是我杀了何贝克上校
Well, I can assure you I killed Colonel Hohlback,
那我担保你会绞刑 不过到那之前 我期望你尽你的职责
Then I guarantee you'll hang, but until then, I expect you to do your duty,
- 是 长官 - 我要前去OP
- Yes, sir, - I want forward OP,
一天3个人看守
Three watches a day,
不然士兵们会变得懒散
Fences fail, troopers get lazy,
- 继续努力 上尉 - 是 长官
- You carry on, captain, - Yes, sir,
我可以为你做什么吗?
Something I can do for you?
我只想说谢谢你救了我
I just came to say thanks for saving my ass,
那没什么
That's the job,
你不睡觉在这看守吗?
How come you don't sleep inside like everyone else?
我想这是敌人会出现的地方
I figure this is where the enemy will show up,
在这里有啥乐子吗?
No telling what kind of fun you could get in out here, huh?
- 你在挑逗我吗? - 没有
- Are you flirting with me, soldier? - No, sir, I don't flirt,
- 没有? - 从来没有
- Never? - Never ever, sir,
- 嗯 一言为定 - 货真价实
- Well, you're the real deal, - The genuine article,
那么你想行动
And you want some action,
虫子出现后你想怎么做就去做
You'll get all the action you want after the Bugs show up,
你知道的...
You know...
...这是我所等待的
...it's all the waiting that gets me,
哦 我懂了
Oh, I see,
你需要有人占有你的心
You need something to occupy your mind,
到这来
Come here,
就是这 做伏地挺身100下
That's good right there, Drop and give me 100,
- 长官? - 你精力旺盛
- Sir? - You got a lot of energy, trooper,
趴下 开始计数
Now get down and start counting,
是 长官
Yes, sir,
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four...
五 六 七
...five, six, seven...
200下
Make it 200,
少了什么吗?
You lose something?
哦 你是新手 所以我...
Yo, you're the new guy, so I...
我可以一起玩吗?
Can we play too?
我去做自己的事
I got mess duty,
- 谢谢把我叫醒 苏达 - 乐意之至
- Thanks for the wake up, Soda, - Pleasure,
你知道你在做什么事吗?
You sure you know what you're doing?
我有个好主意 但是...
Oh, I got a pretty good idea, but...
你知道 熟能生巧
...you know, practice does make perfect,
很好
Nice,
来吧 比利
Come on, Billie,
不 不 别管他 珊蒂 他是个浑球
No, no, forget it, Sandee, He's a jerk,
嘿 珊蒂...
Hey, Sandee...
- 她怎么了? - 何顿跟另外新来的女人搞在一起
- What's with her? - Horton's with the new girl,
- 他想喝点苏达汽水吧 - 战争?
- Sipping some Soda, - Ain't war hell?
谁在那?
Who goes there?
何顿?
Horton?
哦 是你
Oh, it's you,
抱歉
Sorry,
还好吗?
You okay?
不
No,
- 我能做些什么? - 没有
- Anything I can do? - No,
至少让我看看你的下巴怎么了
At least let me take a look at that cut on your chin,
这? 只是刮伤
This? It's just a scratch,
将军希望每个人都没事
General wants everybody tiptop,
- 嘿 乔? - 是?
- Hey, Joe? - Yeah?
你在这里有多久了?
How long have you been out here?
- 感觉好像我一生都在这里 - 是 我明白你的意思
- All my life, it seems like, - Yeah, I know what you mean,
我在这里有八个月了 只看到过两次阳光
I've been here for eight months, and I've only seen the sun twice,
如果你把头盔卸掉也许好些 吉尔
Might be a little easier if you took your helmet off, Jill,
老天 你的手指怎么了?
God, what happened to your fingers?
- 你知道 烧伤的 - 看上去很可怕
- You know, muzzle burn, - That looks really bad,
谁是医护人员?
Hey, who's the medic here anyway, huh?
乔
Hey, Joe,
是?
Yeah?
有没有人说你笑起来很好看
Has anybody ever told you what a nice smile you have?
是吗
Yeah,
可能吧!
Probably,
感觉好点了吗?
Feeling better?
没有
No,
你想要吗?
Do you want to?
- 她怎么了 士官? - 只是流鼻血 长官
- What happened to her, corporal? - Just a nosebleed, sir,
她会没事的
She's gonna be fine,
- 你感觉如何? - 你清楚的
- How do you feel? - You know how I feel,
什么?
What gives?
看上去一对又一对
It looks like we got a couple new couples,
难怪这场战争我们会输 没人在打仗
No wonder we're losing this war, Everyone's fucking instead of fighting,
你在看什么?
What are you looking at?
- 回去工作 - 我会
- Get back to work, - I'll get to work,
- 早安 上尉 - 有什么好的?
- Good morning, captain, - What makes you think so?
为什么? 它们来了?
Why, are we in for it?
- 迟早 - 你有时间吃早餐?
- Sooner or later, - You got time for breakfast?
只要你不期望有愉快的交谈 欢迎一起来
You're welcome to join me, as long as you don't expect cheerful conversation,
你不是个习惯早起的人吗
Not a morning person, huh?
不 我是个一团糟的杀人浑蛋
No, I'm a miserable, murdering bastard,
- 然而那是好的一天 - 那坏日子是怎么样的?
- And that's on a good day, - What's a bad day like?
你对那天特别感兴趣?
Any one day in particular you're interested in?
不
No,
那个超灵者浑球派你来问我的
That second lieu-y send you to question me?
- 迪尔中尉? 他认为我是个白痴 - 是吗?
- Lieutenant Dill? He thinks I'm an idiot, - Are you?
- 我? 嗯 绝对是 - 相信我
- Me? Yeah, Definitely, - Trust me, I got you beat,
我坠入爱河 然后我被降级
Well, I fell in love, and I got busted down from corporal for fraternisation,
- 那家伙是谁? - 这就是我白痴的地方
- So who wants to be a corporal? - Here's the idiot part,
他阵亡了
He got killed,
你真的有超感应力?
You really some kind of psychic?
我猜是吧 不过不像迪尔 是个超灵者
Yeah, Maybe, I guess, Not like Dill, not Psi Corps,
嗯
Well, your fella...
...你预先知道他会阵亡吗?
...did you know he was gonna buy the farm?
不是像那样
It doesn't work that way,
嗯 很好 我想
Well, that's good, I guess,
也许这正是为什么我不信那种空话
Maybe that's why I don't believe in all that bunk,
那些标牌是你那些死去士兵的...
Those tags belong to the troopers that you lost...
...而你戴上它 因为你觉得要对发生的事负责
...and you wear them because you feel responsible for what happened,
那只是你幸运猜中的
That's a lucky guess,
- 你为什么要杀了你的上级 - 你告诉我
- Why'd you kill your CO? - You tell me,
我没那厉害
I'm not that good,
他只会下些愚蠢的命令让那些孩子被杀
He gave some stupid orders that got kids killed,
一次又一次
One day too many, or too many one day,
- 或许这是我的错 - 你该原谅你自己
- Maybe I'm the wheel that broke, - You ought to forgive yourself,
这是战争
It's war,
不要浪费太多时间在我这 士兵
Don't spend too much time around me, trooper,
我受够你跟着我了
I'd hate to end up wearing your tags,
笨蛋
Stupid Bug,
我来看着
You're relieved,
多谢
Thanks,
嘿 士兵?
Hey... Hey, trooper?
谁在那?
Who's that?
皮克
Peck,
士官 你有什么要我做的吗?
Hey, sarge, what do you need?
我需要一个帮手
Well, I could use a hand,
我会为你做的很好
Buddy, anything I can do for you is aces by me,
你可以躺在地上吗?
You think you could lie down on the fl...
- 地上? - 地上 然后到那后面...
- The floor? - Floor, And reach behind the cons...
我知道了 你让我躺在地上然后操作那控制台
I got it, I got it, You want me to lay on the floor and reach behind the console,
好
Okay,
这儿来吧
Here we go,
狗...
Son of a...
这样行吗
How's this?
老天
Oh, God!
救命!
Help!
安静
Gotta keep quiet,
救命! 救命!
Help! Help!
我们可以通讯了
We got com,
We got com.
这里是"三角洲旅馆"哨站呼叫救援舰
This is "三角洲旅馆"哨站 to Fleet Rescue,
快回答
Come in, Fleet Rescue,
这里是"三角洲旅馆"哨站呼叫救援舰
This is "三角洲旅馆"哨站 to Fleet Rescue,
- 这是 - 那些报告怎么了?
- This is... - How's that report coming?
与其写报告不如开始架你的绞首台 达克斯
Well, I'm not so much writing a report as building your gallows, Dax,
- 我不知道你是个木匠 - 改变频率
- I didn't take you for a carpenter, - Shift to Command frequency,
上千年以前有个木匠
There was this other carpenter a few thousand years ago...
...比你和我好
...a better man than you or me,
工作的时候死了
Well, that carpentry business was the death of him,
注意你所做的有没有超过你能承受的
Be careful of what you build and what crosses you bear,
- "三角洲旅馆"哨站呼叫救援舰 - 中尉
- "三角洲旅馆"哨站 to Fleet Command, - Lieutenant,
收到"三角洲旅馆" 这里是舰队指挥中心 完毕
Roger, Hotel Delta, this is Fleet Command. Over.
701机动部队 请求救援接应
This is the 701 st Mobile lnfantry, Bravo Company, requesting pickup,
你得排队 这里到处都有部队需要救援
Take a number, MI. We got stragglers all over the planet.
- 你叫什么名字? - 舰队中尉玛丽 克雷高夫
- What's your name, sailor? - Fleet Lieutenant Mary Klinghof.
- 我也帮不了你们 - 给我听着
- Getting smart won't help you, jarhead. - You listen up, fruit fly,
我是杰克 高登 夏福特将军
This is General Jack Gordon Shepherd,
如果你不优先救援
And if somebody doesn't make this pickup their priority...
那我会把你们列在我的优先名单
...I'm gonna make it my priority to come down...
从你开始整死你们这些浑蛋
...and chew out some Fleet-ass, starting with you,
对不起 长官 我不知道在跟谁说话
Sorry, sir, I didn't know who I was talking to.
- 那是因为你是个白痴 - 是的
- That's because you're a moron, - Yeah,
是的 长官 但是我们有很多伤患
Yes, sir, but we got a lot of wounded out there.
伤患先走 别再找藉口了
The wounded come first, Any excuses after that come out of your butt,
结束
Shepherd, out,
皮克在哪? 我要给他个荣誉勋章
Where's Peck? I'm gonna give him a medal,
- 睡着了 - 嗯
- Asleep, sir, Dead on his feet, - Well, he's earned it,
- 门修好了没 - 我们都在等着 士官
- Any day on that door, Brick, - We're all waiting for something, sarge,
- 但是这不是门 - 漂亮
- But it ain't the door, - Outstanding,
不是你 士兵
Not you, trooper.
- 猜的好 - 我们都将战死
- Lucky guess. - We're all gonna die.
- 你知道荣誉是什么? - 这没用的啦
- What would you know about glory? - It doesn't work that way.
- 如果他不战斗 杀了他! - 不!
- If he won't fight, shoot him! - No!
- 萨哈拉 - 我看不到他
- Sahara. - I haven't seen him.
- 醒醒 - 是我的错
- Wake up. - The wheel that broke.
醒醒
Wake up.
多来点别害羞
Give me a little more, Don't be shy, Come on,
别急 吃得到的
Yeah, Oh, trouble at the trough,
这样不好看
It's gonna get ugly,
- 啥吃了托尔 - 不是你
- What's eating Tor, huh? - Not you,
我想你是对的 战争使人古怪
Yeah, I guess you're right, War does some weird things to people,
一切还好吗?
Everything okay?
我我我 没事
No, I'm... Yeah, I'm fine,
- 你看上去在发抖 士兵 - 是的 有些事情有点不对
- You look a little shaky, trooper, - Yeah, something's not right,
就是因为你被敌人包围
That's what they call it when you're behind enemy lines,
我感觉比那更糟糕
It feels worse than that,
哦 是不是别的超感应力出现了?
Oh, is this another one of your psychic hot flashes?
好像托尔有些不对劲
It seems like Tor has changed,
因为他没吃饭?
Because he wouldn't take Brick's bait? About time,
- 很突然 士官 - 像你今早呕吐吗
- lt seems sudden, sarge, - Like you puking your guts out?
我想我会弄清原因的
I guess I'm coming down with something,
我好奇那是为啥
I wonder what that could be?
我的胃好像打结了
There's a big knot where my stomach used to be,
士官 我刚才碰了医护兵的手 看到了一些事情
Sarge, I barely touched the medic's hand just now, and I saw something,
- 你看到什么? - 一些可怕的事情
- You saw something? - Something terrible,
- 也许你是疯了 - 我也爱你 士官
- Maybe you're just going crazy, - I love you too, sarge,
当女人怀孕时就会古怪
Girls get wacky when they're pregnant,
突然间他们就会知道所有的事情
Suddenly, they know everything about everything,
哦 天啊
Oh, Jesus,
是啊 你开始成为超灵者了啊
Yeah, you're about as psychic as a doorknob, trooper,
你准备好了?
You ready?
我有些累
I'm kind of tired,
- 我会帮助你的 - 好 谢谢
- I'll give you a hand, - Oh, thanks,
我的鞋
Oh, my shoe,
别管它了
Don't worry about it,
- 你怕洗澡 奥特? - 有啥关系?
- Are you scared to shower, Otter? - What does it matter?
再过几小时我们可以回家了
We're going home in a few hours anyway,
嗨 伙计
Hi, guys,
上帝 这是...
Holy God, what the...
老天
Oh, God, Oh, God,
开门! 开门! 我们会死在这里的!
Open the door! Open the door! We're gonna die in here!
开门!
Open the door!
上尉 我想和你谈谈 但是这好像有点不可思议
Captain, I need to talk to you, but it's gonna sound crazy,
- 好 说吧 - 看 长官...
- Well, spit it out, trooper, - Look, sir...
...我知道我不被认为是个超灵者...
...l know I'm not really supposed to be psychic...
不过我有一种不好的预感
...but I have this terrible feeling,
- 长官 - 稍息
- Yes, sir, - As you were,
我想我们遇到一些情况 需要超灵军官关注
We have a situation here that requires the attention of Military lntelligence,
- 告诉他 - 今早...
- Tell him, - This morning, in the mess...
...我无意中碰到了格列佛的手 我看到了影像
...l accidentally touched Griff's hand, I might've had a vision,
又再扮超灵者 二等兵?
Playing psychic again, private?
可以先不预设立场吗 中尉?
Could you keep an open mind here, lieutenant?
她有重要的事情
This trooper's got information that's vital,
有几个士兵近来表现得很奇怪
Some of the troopers have been acting a little strange lately,
描述一下你所看到的
Describe what you saw,
那不是人 他是一些其他的东西
He wasn't a man, He was some other thing,
也许1000个 他传给...
Maybe 1000 things, Somehow he was connected...
托尔和珊蒂和何顿 还有新来的女孩 苏达
...to Tor and Sandee and Horton and that new girl, Soda,
我一直弄不清楚 然而这感觉很尖锐
I've always been pretty fuzzy, sir, and this came through sharp as a knife,
中尉 我知道我不像你一样是超灵者
Lieutenant, I know I'm not a real psychic like you,
事实上 我怀孕了 我毫无头绪
In fact, I just found out I'm pregnant, and I didn't have a clue,
- 你怀孕了? - 是 长官 恐怕是的
- You're pregnant? - Yes, sir, I'm afraid so,
你应该知道我们研究过...
You might be interested to know that in our studies...
...怀孕可以提高超感应力
...pregnancy has been shown to heighten psychic ability,
那就糟了 我希望我是错的
That's too bad because I'd really like to be wrong,
是的 我也是 但我也有相同的感觉
Yes, me too, but I keep having the same feeling,
是什么?
What is it?
我们会被它们消灭
They're coming to wipe us out,
这怎么说?
What's so new about that?
我是说整个人类种族 它们有个计划
I mean the whole species, everything human, And they have a plan,
在那场战争之后...
Look, after what I did in the battle...
...我不能确定自我
...l wasn't very sure of myself anymore,
我想每个人都认为我砸了
And I just figured everybody thought I'd just cracked,
昨天 我就应该同意中尉
Yesterday, I might have been inclined to agree...
应该是我搞砸了中尉
...but that would've been me screwing up, lieutenant,
谢谢 长官
Thank you, sir,
我得立即向将军报告
I'll get on this matter with General Shepherd immediately,
哦 士兵...
Oh, and, trooper...
做的很好
...that was some good work,
长官
Sir,
夏福特将军?
General Shepherd?
你在这干什么?
What are you doing in here?
杰克将军和我在聊天
General Jack and l were just having a chat,
迪尔 你在这里做什么?
What are you doing here, Dill?
你和夏福特?
You and Shepherd?
很难相信吗?
Is that so hard to believe?
将军?
General?
夏福特将军?
General Shepherd?
将军...
General...
他们在你身体里 天呐
They're inside of you, Oh, God,
退后 否则我轰爆开你的头
Back up, or I'll drill your damn skull,
回来! 从那门走开
Get back! Get away from the door,
走开
Get away,
该死的 你们都被捕了...
You bastards, You're all under arrest...
...因为谋杀 暴乱 反叛联邦
...for murder, sedition, for treason against the Federation...
我不会杀你们不过你们会付出代价
Oh, and you're gonna pay because we're not gonna kill you,
不不不 你看 我们位置有利
Oh, no, No, you see, we got special places for things like you...
他们抓到你
...where they cut you up,
但是他们让你活着...
But they keep you alive while they cut you up...
...他们就能知道什么能逼你 什么能使你生病
...so they can see what makes you tick, and they'll see what makes you sick,
我会在那 是 我会去那看...
And I'll be there, Oh, yeah, I'm gonna be there to see...
你被逮捕了 达克斯
You're under arrest, Dax,
罪名?
On what charge?
谋杀
Murder,
- 达克斯上尉 发生什么事了? - 不准和囚犯讲话
- Captain Dax, what's happening? - No talking to the prisoner,
把他关起来 跟我保证
Keep him covered, You gave me your word, Dax,
是什么让你认为我做了这 将军?
What makes you think I had anything to do with this, general?
- 把他锁上 上士 - 是 长官
- Lock him up, sergeant, - Yes, sir, With pleasure, sir,
- 快从这逃出去 萨哈拉 - 走
- Get out of here now, Sahara, - Move it,
你知道该做什么 比利
You know what to do, Billie,
是 长官
Yes, sir,
你在干什么 比利?
Why are you doing this, Billie?
不只是你和我 是我们所有人
It's not you and me, It's gonna happen to all of us,
你想要跟那扇门生孩子吗?
You trying to make a baby with my barracks door, private?
萨哈拉 她不想要 但我要给她个虫子
Sahara, she don't want it, but I gotta give her the Bug,
- 你秀逗了吗 - 不
- There's a wire loose in your head, - No, it's a little piece of God,
不再是过去深信联邦...
Not like the one people used to believe in, or the Federation...
充满了我 我可以感觉到自己飘了起来
...and it's filling me up, I can sort of feel myself floating away,
你疯了
Kid, you're not making any sense,
当你醒了你就会明白的
You'll understand when you wake up,
我醒来的时候?
When I wake up?
- 不要抵抗了 - 门都没有
- Don't fight, - That'll be the day,
不!
No!
你孤单吗? 上尉
You lonely, captain?
比利 不要 求求你
Billie, please don't, Please,
到底怎么了 士官?
What the hell's going on, sergeant?
- 虫子在里面 长官 - 在这里?
- The Bugs are inside, sir, - lnside the perimeter?
不是的 长官
No, sir,
在我体内
Inside me,
士官 不! 不!
Sergeant, no! No!
钥匙
Keys,
- 那虫子究竟是什么? - 天呐
- What the hell kind of Bug is that? - Jesus,
他们侵入体内 然后接管一切 也许这能解释这一切
One that gets inside and takes over, Maybe it can tell us something,
你在说什么啊?
What are you talking about?
在这发生的一是早该预料到的
Everything that happened here was supposed to happen.
虫族把我们带到这然后制造武器
The Bugs brought us here to create a weapon.
- 什么武器? - 夏福特!
- What kind of weapon? - Shepherd!
他会把这个带到联邦去
He could bring this to the top of the Federation!
我们必须杀了将军
We gotta kill the general,
手榴弹!
Fire in the hole!
你会死的!
You're gonna die!
他们没那么容易杀死 是吗?
They don't kill so easy, do they?
- 你会死的! - 他们不像我们 长官
- You're gonna die! - They're not like us, sir,
再也不是了 他们是虫子
Not anymore, They're Bugs,
你会死的! 你会死的!
You're gonna die! You're gonna die!
他们关了那反应堆
They shut down the reactors,
珊蒂?
Sandee?
手榴弹!
Grenade!
萨哈拉 你还好吗?
Sahara, you okay?
可怜的家伙
Poor creatures,
我们为什么必须消灭你?
Why must we destroy you?
我会告诉你为什么
I'll tell you why,
造物的潮流向前迈进
Order is the tide of creation...
不过你的种族
...but yours is a species...
崇拜个人胜过群体
...that worships the one over the many,
以拥有智能为荣
You glorify your intelligence...
...因为如此你们相信
...because it allows you to believe anything,
你们的命运
That you have a destiny,
你们的权利
That you have a right,
你们的源由
That you have a cause,
你们是独特的
That you are special,
你们是伟大的
That you are great,
但是事实上
But in truth...
你们生而疯狂
...you are born insane,
充满苦痛
And such misery...
以致于不能
...cannot be allowed...
散播
...to spread,
杀光他们
Kill them all!
萨哈拉! 解决将军!
Sahara! You get the general!
- 将军夏福特! - 是我!
- General Shepherd! - That's me!
你不能带他走! 不管怎么做都不能让他上船
You can't take him! Whatever you do, don't let him onboard!
将军
Hey, general!
听着 她需要医疗
Listen up, She needs medical attention,
你杀了将军!
You just killed a general officer, mister!
在那有很多将军 驾驶员
Lots of generals out there, flyboy!
这个士兵有很多对联邦重要的情报
This trooper's got information vital to the survival of the Federation!
她必须不计任何代价安全的到达! 懂了吗
She must reach safety at all costs! You get me?
是 长官
Yes, sir!
- 我们走! - 他们太多了 达克斯
- Let's go! - There are too many of them, Dax!
你必须要告诉他们你所看到的 告诉他们有新虫种
You gotta tell them what you saw, You gotta tell them about the new Bug!
你留在这会没命的
You stay here, you'll die!
杀人犯是不能回去的
Murderers don't go home,
达克斯!
Dax!
达克斯 是一个出色的士兵
Dax. More than a soldier, not just a man.
一位联邦英雄
A hero of the Federation.
为我们的战斗他献出了他的生命...
He gave his life so we could fight...
每个人都应铭记这句话：
...and these words for us to live by:
"不要为我流泪 我的荣誉长存"
"Shed no tears for me. My glory lives forever. "
你也将得到这荣誉...
And now you too can live the glory...
因为在机动部队很容易成就一个英雄
...because it's easy to be a hero in the Mobile Infantry.
许多像你这样的男男女女都愿意签名
Men and women like you are signing up every day...
...为联邦战斗 维护银河
... to serve the Federation and save the galaxy!
是时候成为一份子?
Isn't it time you did your part?
可爱的孩子
Beautiful baby, ma'am,
谢谢 士官
Thank you, sergeant,
想想你的朋友和老师会有多注意你
Think how impressed friends and teachers will be!
每个人都热爱公民
Everyone loves a citizen!
像我这样小士兵
Little trooper likes me,
签个名 有一天他们也会认为你是英雄
Sign up, and one day they'll call you a hero too!
快来吧 我们需要新血
Hurry up, spud, We need fresh meat for the grinder,
不要为我流泪 我的荣誉长存
Shed no tears for me. My glory lives forever.